1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/txtField_Email"), "agung.priyadi@gtech.digital")
17. setText(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/txtField_Verification Code"), "")
21. click(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/btn_Send"))
25. verifyTextPresent("The verification code has been sent, please check in the mailbox.", false)
29. verifyElementHasAttribute(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/btn_Continue"), "disabled", 5)
33. takeScreenshot()
37. closeBrowser()